Joey saw it in Major Aglipay's
belongings.
That's it.
That's the video
that will free Father!
Could this be what your Korean
friend was talking about?
It's Theresa.
Bro, what happened?
Did you catch Theresa?
Not yet, but I know I'm close.
Me too, I have good news too.
The broken flash drive,
there's a copy.
Where is it?
Joey sent it to the attorney
for evidence.
Just a little bit, Father,
you can go home.
We'll be together again.
I heard you need help
with your husband's case.
I don't want to bother you
anymore.
There's new evidence
that just came out.
Delgado got new evidence.
Find out what it is right away.
I need to see Berdugo.
He's meeting with his new
partners
at the end of the month.
The video evidence,
are you going to release it
to the public?
Yeah.
Which means...
she will be a wanted woman.
I know you what you want
to happen,
but I can't ignore
the new evidence.
Because of the evidence
that came out
in the case of Major
Miguel Delgado,
the Court has made a decision,
Ka-Tiradas.
The former police officer
has been proven innocent.
It's better for me to leave now
because the movements of
Berdugo's group are restricted.
Golda, thank you very much
for your help.
You fixed my mother and father's
relationship.
And even though your statement
was rejected,
I'm still grateful
that you did it.
Why are you still there?
Leave now.
We're getting ready, Boss.
Leave now
and don't come back while
the situation is still hot.
I don't want our operations
to be jeopardized
just because of you two.
No one knows we're here.
Maybe I can just hide here.
I thought you were smart?
Do you think no one else
will see you there?
Leave now if you don't want me
to force you out.
Leave now!
Thanks to you guys,
because of you, Father is free.
We won.
You, of all people,
you know you're close to me.
Come on.
Sir Oppa, thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Andrew, thank you.
Boss Budol.
Welcome.
I have to go.
You know, I'm working on a new
lead where I can find Theresa.
I'm hoping that it pays off
this time.
Okay, you be safe.
Also, once you catch Theresa,
you ask all of them who their
mastermind is.
Gotta put all of them in jail.
Yes.
Why are you following me?
I'm going with you.
Let's go.
You know what the problem is?
What?
You give up too easily instead
of chasing what you want.
- No, I don't.
- No, you did!
You just left the house because
you've given up on Joey.
Well, she doesn't like me.
She likes someone else.
Did she say that?
See?
Then why not?
You will never know
unless you ask.
Is that how you make the moves
with the girls?
You just push, push, push?
If you're asking...
if I go after what I want,
then yes.
I will not stop
until she's mine.
Come in.
Peter.
I was going to talk to you two.
What?
Why?
Maybe this is the last time
we'll be together.
Why?
I'm going home.
I want to be with my family.
I understand.
Of course, you've been dreaming
of that for a long time,
haven't you?
Just call if you need anything.
I'll be right there.
Same here.
Thank you to both of you.
How's that?
Our lives are back to normal.
So, you are going back
to Tirada Express as Boss Idol.
And you, of course, will work.
Then, Jin Ho,
his search will continue,
and he will definitely catch
that Theresa.
I'll just call you when
it's not too hot and safe.
Okay.
Don't be pissed off.
Just be grateful,
he's just asking you to hide.
We know what can happen.
I'm a little hesitant
about Jin Ho searching
for Theresa Park
because he doesn't want
to cooperate with the police.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Of course, he might want to get
Theresa on his own.
But the thing is, he's Interpol,
and he has to cooperate
with the police.
You know, I feel like...
there's something personal
going on
in his search for Theresa.
I wouldn't be like a mouse
hiding from a cat
if it weren't for the person
who took the video.
I want my revenge.
That's going to happen.
We'll find her and make her pay.
That's exactly what I'm going
to do.
I'll even take a video of her
while I'm killing her.
Call it poetic justice.
Well, maybe that's what happens
when you're in law enforcement.
Just like what happened
to Father.
That's personal.
Oh well, I'm sure that
when Jin Ho catches Theresa,
he'll also find out
where her accomplices are,
and then everyone in the
syndicate will be caught.
Our lives will be peaceful.
Who's that?
Hurry up!
Get out of the car.
Get out!
Joey, I'll just check
our booking.
I'll just go there.
I'll just wait for you.
Andrew,
thanks for all your help?
At least, now your life
will be peaceful
because there won't be
an immature person
bothering you anymore.
Well, about that...
You're so sensitive sometimes.
And I get it,
it's really foul,
so I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if I misjudged you
just because you're younger.
I actually think that you're
strong and smart,
and you're determined
in everything you do.
Also,
everybody's lucky to have you
by their side.
Wow!
Coming from Boss Budol, really?
I'm just praising you now.
Can we get rid of
that "Boss Budol?"
No.
No, but seriously,
thank you very much because
your opinion of me has changed.
I, too, have changed
my opinion of you.
I only knew you because
of three traits.
Irritable, hot-headed,
and moody.
Wow, you're being sorry
with that.
Wait, let me finish.
I'll also say that it
has also changed
because I saw that you care too.
I'm so happy you caught me.
I need you.
I'm in trouble.
I need you, Baby.
But I have some advice for you.
Smile often and have high energy
than normal.
- That's it.
- Like this?
Yes.
Like a celebrity,
outside the salon poster.
Let me see.
That.
- Show me a smile.
- Joey!
- Show me a smile...
- Smile?
Let's go, our ride is ready.
So, see you around, Boss Budol?
See you, JoeyOnDuty.
I'm done falling for your games.
We had a deal.
We were supposed to escape
together, right?
But you...
You left me.
I was scared.
I didn't know who to trust.
I doubted you.
I'm sorry.
But you...
You're the only one
who didn't give up on me.
But you...
you did everything to find me.
Yes.
So I found you now.
To bring you back to Scorpio
so you can be punished
for running away
and stealing from us.
And stealing this from me.
Really?
Is that really what you want?
To watch me get punished?
Tortured?
Can you really live with that?
I know you still love me.
I know you can't let go of me.
So instead of handing me over
to die,
come with me.
You and I,
we fight back against everyone
who wants to bring us apart
and bring us down.
Let's finish what we started
together.
Join me.
Join me, Baby.
Mother!
Okay.
It's a good thing your
break isn't over yet,
and you'll be with us
for a long time.
You came home right on time.
The bathroom upstairs is dirty.
And the grass here in our
backyard is already tall.
You know what you're going
to do.
What are you saying?
I'm not going to order
my daughter around.
We're going to have a QT.
What cutie?
I didn't say you were cute.
What I said was, QT.
Your father went buffering
again.
Do you know why?
He doesn't know what QT means.
What is QT?
Quality time, Father.
Of course,
Mother and I missed you.
Let's have some quality time.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on, come on, come on.
Wait a minute?
Someone's calling.
Peter, why?
Joey, are you home already?
Yes, I just got home.
That's good, but Jin Ho,
do you have any news?
Is he home?
He hasn't replied yet.
Wow.
You're so clingy to your Oppa.
I might get jealous.
Hey, who are you talking to?
What jealousy are you
talking about?
It's just Peter.
Peter, Father.
Hi, Peter.
Hello, Major.
Thank you so much
for your help with Joey.
I'm free now.
Uncle, that's nothing.
I'm just making up because,
of course,
your daughter is a good person.
And of course,
I can't forsake her either.
Besides, I don't want her hurt.
You know that she's important
to me, so...
You know, you're really an
oversharer.
Father gets it.
Okay, let's talk later.
Don't miss me, okay? Bye.
Come on. Sit down, sit down.
- Yes, I'm hungry. Let's go.
- Come on.
They even mentioned
missing each other.
Let's pray first.
Lord, thank you for today.
Thank you again
because we're together.
Thank you for the food
in front of us today.
Amen.
Okay, how about this...
Godfather and the fallen deal.
It's still fresh and a big name.
That's possible.
Hey, that's for the anniversary
expose.
- Right.
- For sure, it'll be trending.
Andrew, what do you think?
Here he is.
- Hello?
- Boss?
What's this, Boss Andrew?
It seems like he doesn't want
to be with us.
He probably wants to be
with his other team.
What are you saying?
I thought of something.
Why don't we interview
Major Miguel Delgado?
Andrew, we're an exposé show.
We're not Tito Boy.
Or maybe he just wants
to see Joey again?
Right?
Didn't it cross your mind
that that's okay?
We'll have a new segment,
a new angle.
So that the people involved
can have a voice, too.
Possible.
Good.
There's a human angle.
It seems like there's
an emotional connection.
- Right!
- Right?
That's it, isn't it?
Kyle, come on, make a list.
Let's make a list of names
that we can interview.
Donald Trump!
- Hey! Okay!
- That's it!
- Who else?
- Kanye West.
- Awesome, awesome, yeah.
- Okay?
Who else? One more.
Think of someone else?
Okay.
I know who he wants
to interview.
Joey.
Is that the Korean guy,
your crush?
I don't have a crush on him.
Jin Ho is just really funny.
Father.
Well, it's good that you
don't have a crush.
Poor Peter.
Mother, you too.
You're something else.
And Mother,
Peter is just my friend.
Buddy, best friend!
We're just like siblings.
What? Best friend?
Like a brother?
I don't think so.
What did he say earlier?
- "She's important to me."
- There you go.
- Is that just best friends?
- Yes.
- You're something else.
- Yes, Tito Boy.
Father became a gossipmonger
when he was released.
No, but Peter is also important
to me.
All of them.
Jin Ho and Andrew, too.
Because what we went through
was so hard.
Besides, they really became
my true friends.
You know, Joey, you're lucky.
It's hard to find those
kinds of friends,
the ones who aren't always there
just because they're just happy.
Your mother was right.
Friends like them, you should
take good care of them.
I hope we can be together again
not because of any problem.
That's true.
Come on, let's finish that.
Hey, Mother,
let me help you with that.
There are still some glasses.
Okay, okay.
Now that we don't have to worry
about Lisa,
let's focus on the real problem.
I can't believe
he's making headlines
instead of rotting underground.
He just got free,
but he'll never escape us.
He'll bother us again.
He can't make us look weak,
Matias,
especially now that our new deal
is in motion.
I'll take care of that, Berdugo.
Miguel, I know you.
You won't be at peace
if you don't catch the syndicate
that's after you.
I'm going back to service.
I'm going to finish this fight.
By the authority vested in me,
I hereby reinstate you to active
service, Major Miguel Delgado.
Where is Joey?
- Do you need anything from her?
- What do you need?
I tried to keep him out
of this mess,
but he wanted this,
and I can't afford a weapon
pointed at us,
even if he's family.
Like what they say,
we're just getting
to the exciting part.
Ready, Berdugo.
Have you thought of a way
to expose the syndicate?
You know, Andrew...